Open your lips, ask Jesus to give you prayer language.
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Give me a tongue.
He holds the key to my life,
When sickness and sorrow
Seem to take my soul away,
He holds the key to my life.
When sickness and sorrow
Seem to take my soul away,
He holds the key to my life.
When sickness and sorrow
Seem to take my soul away,
He holds the key to my life.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Even without asking, Jesus is working out the answer.
Whatever situation you are in, whatever challenges you are in,
whatever difficulty or pain - it could be sickness -
remember, a demon is behind it.
It could be failure - remember, a demon is behind it.
It could be limitation in progress - remember, a demon is behind it.
Right now, open your lips and begin to rebuke this demon.
Demon!
In the name of Jesus!
Rebuke them!
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Whatever means demons might have used to connect you to himself.
Whatever way satan might have used to connect your career to himself,
to connect your business, to connect your future,
to connect your marital life to himself - begin to break it, right now.
Break it!
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Watch the screen of your television, you can see the proof that satan
and his agents are no match for the all consuming fire of God.
Viewers all around the world, in mercy you have not been excluded, touch the screen
of your television right now and receive your deliverance, your healing
by faith in Jesus' name.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I'm not saying words, I'm praying prayer.
Just repeat after me:
whatever means, whatever way satan might have used
to connect you to himself - begin to rebuke it!
Break it!
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Viewers all over the world, continue to break it!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Whatever way - it could be immorality, failure or unfaithfulness -
whatever way satan might have used to connect you to himself,
begin to break that relationship!
Break it!
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Viewers all over the world, continue to pray along with Prophet TB Joshua right now.
As it is happening here in the SCOAN headquarters, it will happen wherever you are by faith.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Remember, satan has many ways he uses to connect people to himself.
It could be disobedience - he uses disobedience to connect you.
He can use hatred. These are his weapons.
He can use immorality. These are his weapons.
Once you are connected, you become an agent.
Now, we want to break all these - all these means!
Begin to mention those things satan uses to connect you to himself.
You know those things, you know them. Mention them.
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Viewers around the world, join prophet T.B. Joshua in this mass prayer section.
The power of God is removing them from the kingdom of darkness into the kingdom of light.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Viewers, whatever way satan might have used to connect you to himself -
it could be disobedience.
These are weapons - weapons of disobedience, hatred, greediness,
killing, stealing, destruction, immorality, disobedience.
Whatever way satan might have used,
right now, begin to break the connection!
Break the connection!
Say - you satan, I break the connection!
That connection - break it!
Viewers all over the world, break it!
Break it!
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Viewers all over the world, what you are seeing is the manifestation of the evil spirit.
People are vomiting out all poisonous substances that has
been deposited in their systems, they have been set free from the kingdom of darkness.
As you are watching the screen of your television, step in faith believing that
your case will not escape the anointing of God.
Distance is not a barrier, Jesus Christ is reachable, you can touch Him wherever you are.
Right now touch the screen of your television and believe.
Break the connection!
It could be greediness, selfishness, killing or stealing.
It could be disobedience or unfaithfulness.
It could be hatred, stealing, killing, greediness or immorality - break it!
He holds the key to my life,
When sickness and sorrow
Seem to take my soul away,
He holds the key to my life.
When sickness and sorrow
Seem to take my soul away,
He holds the key to my life.
When sickness and sorrow
Seem to take my soul away,
He holds the key to my life.
When sickness and sorrow
Seem to take my soul away,
He holds the key to my life.
When sickness and sorrow
Seem to take my soul away,
He holds the key to my life.
If satan does not have connection,
if there is no wire between you and satan,
satan cannot even touch you.
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Some of his connections - disobedience, unfaithfulness
immorality, stealing, killing, destruction - these are the connection.
You are his tools and agent.
Now this is personal confession, open your lips and begin to disconnect yourself.
Whatever way satan might have used to connect you to himself,
whether hatred, unfaithfulness or lying -
maybe sometimes you lie.
Whatever way satan might have used or is using to connect you to himself,
open your lips and begin to break that connection!
I break it, right now!
Open your lips, in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus!
Begin to break the connection!
Break the connection!
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Say - I break the connection!
Break the connection!
Begin to break the connection!
Break it!
In the name of Jesus!
We are talking of character.
God's Word reflects His character.
We are talking of salvation, now.
Something more than miracles. We are talking of the salvation of your soul.
That is what we are praying for.
The way satan connects you to himself and begin to toy with you...
You know tow vehicle - he will begin to tow you everywhere.
You become an agent. At night you say that somebody came and hit you.
Somebody came and had an affair with you but you cannot resist.
Why? Because satan has connected you to himself.
This is the experience many of you are having -
in your dream, when you wake up, you say: "Ah, my guest slept with me last night!"
And this is a guy in the physical, he respects you.
But at night he will ride you.
The reason you cannot resist is because you have become an agent.
Satan has connected you to himself and he has used this weapons -
weapons of unrighteousness, disobedience, immorality,
lying, stealing. Begin to disconnect yourself!
Disconnect yourself!
In the name of Jesus!
Say: "I disconnect myself!
Whatever weapon, whatever way satan might have used
to connect me to himself!" -
begin to disconnect yourself, in the name of Jesus!
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Viewers all over the world, I know, we are carrying you along - glory be to God!
It is happening in your home.
Those weapons satan uses are the fruits of the flesh -
immorality, disobedience, unfaithfulness, hatred,
unforgiving spirit - these are weapons.
And once he is using this to connect you to himself,
he will begin to tow you like a vehicle - you know, like towing a vehicle.
Anywhere he tows you, anywhere he drags you - you go, you become an agent. He can say: "Go!" or: "Сome!"
because you are being connected to satan. So therefore,
whatever way satan might have used to connect you to himself,
begin to disconnect yourself!
Viewers all over the world, begin to disconnect yourself!
Begin to disconnect yourself!
Disconnect yourself!
In the name of Jesus!
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Disconnect yourself as the man of God has said.
The evidence of the grace of Calvary is what we are witnessing in the life of people,
as they are vomiting, shouting, screaming and manifesting
coming out of their darkness. God is exposing the darkness in the life of the people
through the faculty of the man of God right now. Stay connected -
everywhere in the world, wherever you are viewing, stay connected.
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
He holds the key to my life,
When sickness and sorrow
Seen to take my breath away,
He holds the key to my life.
When sickness and sorrow
Seem to take my soul away,
He holds the key to my life.
When sickness and sorrow
Seem to take my soul away,
He holds the key to my life.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Say: "Thank You for my salvation."
Right now, begin to confess these.
I submit myself to be an agent of truth,
an agent of love,
an agent of faithfulness,
and obedience - begin to confess it.
In Jesus' name, confess it.
I submit myself today to be an agent of faithfulness,
an agent of truth, kindness, faithfulness and self-control.
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
So, help me God!
I submit myself to be an agent of truth, faithfulness, obedience,
love and self-control.
So, help me God.
In Jesus' name.
Confess it!
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Viewers around the world, continue to watch the screen.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Let me pray with you.
Father, we thank You for salvation, now.
Salvation, now.
In the name of Jesus!
Send the light,
Oh Jehovah!
Send the light into my soul.
In the name of Jesus!
Send the light,
Oh Jehovah,
Send the light into my soul.
In the name of Jesus!
Send the light,
Oh Jehovah,
Send the light into my soul.
Let there be light!
In Jesus Christ's name.
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Anywhere in your life!
Whatever that has to do with you, anywhere there is an atom of darkness -
right now, I command light there, in the name of Jesus!
I prophesy to your life - let there be light!
I prophesy to your life - let there be light in your business!
Let there be light in your career!
Let there be light in your future!
Let there be light in your marital life!
Let there be light in your family!
Let there be light in your career!
Let there be light!
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name.
Begin to walk in the light of your testimony.
Walk in the light of your testimony.
Begin to confess your release!
Confess your release!
I'm released!
My business is released!
My health is restored!
My career is restored!
My family, my marital life are restored!
I'm released!
In Jesus' name.
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Tell your neighbour: "Сhange your words and your thoughts, as a victor."
How does a victor talk?
Defeat and failure are things of the past.
I'm justified!
I'm no longer condemned!
I'm born again!
I'm redeemed!
In Jesus Christ's name.
SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
We believe you have been inspired
by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more
of God's power at work in our generation today.
And stay up to date with the latest prophecies,
deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives,
Changing nations and Changing the world
TT:Lizz ndung'u 23/01/2017
RV: PavelTatyanaZheleznyakov 22/06/2018